rebatly.com 2018-08-22

# Privacy Policy | Savings United

**Data Protection**

**-Savings United-**

  1. **   ** **The Website Provider of savings-united.com**

1.1.             Savings United GmbH, Große Elbstraße 145D, 22767 Hamburg, Tel.: +49 (0) 40 60945766, E-Mail: contact@savings-united.com (hereinafter referred to as “Provider”) operates the portal which can be accessed at **_savings-united.com_** with its sub-pages (hereinafter referred to as “Portal”).

1.2.             The Provider takes the protection of your personal data very seriously and complies with the applicable data protection regulations, in particular, the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), German Datenschutzgrundverordnung (DSGVO) and the German Federal Data Protection Act Bundesdatenschutzgesetz (BDSG). The following statement gives you an overview of how the Provider guarantees this protection and what kind of data is collected for which purpose.

1.3.             If you have any questions or problems with data protection matters, please contact our Data Protection Officer (DPO): Patrick Rayermann, Gesellschaft für Compliance und Datenschutz mbH Certitut,  
Hackenstr. 7, 80331 Munich, Germany, Tel: +49 (0) 89 21541600 dsb@certitut.de

  2. **                Collection, processing, and use of general data**

2.1.             The Provider automatically collects and saves information when accessing the portal or its subpages, which your browser transmits to the Provider, provided that the corresponding functions are not deactivated. This data is evaluated exclusively to ensure a trouble-free operation of the portal and to improve the offer and do not allow the Provider any conclusion on your person. This data is:

  * Anonymised IP address of the device
  * Date and time of the server request
  * Name of the retrieved files or information
  * Transferred amount of data
  * Operating system and information about the Internet browser of the device accessing the portal
  * Type of the device
  * Screen resolution of the device
  * Battery level of the device
  * CPU usage of the device

  3. **                 Personal data**

3.1.             Personal data is only collected, processed and used as part of the use of the portal as described below. Personal data are all individual details about personal or factual circumstances of a specific or identifiable natural person (not including: legal entities, such as a GmbH or AG). The personal data include, in particular, information such as the name, address, e-mail address or professional circumstances of a person.

  4. **                 Collection, processing, and use of personal data**

_4.1.             _The Provider collects, processes and stores your personal data if you notify the Provider when you contact him (e.g. by e-mail or telephone). In the context of the interaction with you, mentioned above, the required data will be collected. In addition, further data can be queried, which are helpful for the consultation and the need-to-know information; the entry of this data is voluntary and marked accordingly. The Provider uses the data provided by you to process your inquiries or contractual matters. In order that you do not repeatedly have to provide the same information to the Provider in the case of inquiries or ongoing consultations, they are stored as long as they are needed to clarify the inquiry or the customer relationship. The data processing is carried out on the basis of Art. 6§1 sentence 1 lit. b DSGVO, if it serves the purpose of contract execution or preparatory measures. Insofar as you have consented to the collection of data and data processing, the processing of data is governed by Art. 6 §1 sentence 1 lit. a DSGVO.

4.2.             All personal data is stored or processed on servers within the EU (Belgium). A transfer of data to offices outside the EU takes place only in the framework permitted under Art. 44 DSGVO (GDPR conformity).

4.3.            You have a right to object to the collection of data for direct marketing purposes. In order to exercise this right of revocation, you send us an informal message to **contact@savings-united.com** stating your email address and the website you visited in which your intention to revoke is expressed.

  5. **                 Data transmission to third parties**

5.1.             The Provider will only pass on your personal data to third parties in the following cases:

5.1.1.           If the transfer is otherwise necessary for the provision of a service requested or commissioned by you (for example: newsletter subscription); or

5.1.2.          If there is a mandatory administrative or judicial order.

  6. **                 Deletion and correction of data**

6.1.             Upon request or termination of the contract with the Provider, your personal data will be deleted immediately, if the non-tax or commercial legal storage or documentation obligations are in conflict or the securing of the legitimate interests of the Provider is at risk.

6.2.            Until all contractual obligations have been fulfilled and your data is required, there is no entitlement to data deletion.

6.3.             If the data is faulty, it will be corrected if known or requested.

  7. **                 Right to information and further rights**

7.1.             Upon request, the Provider gives you particular information about:

  * The collection of personal data,
  * The purpose of the data processing,
  * The categories of processed data, as well as
  * Where applicable, the beneficiaries to whom data is disclosed due to legal obligations or contractual relationships.

7.2.             Upon request, you will receive from the Provider a copy of the data collected and processed by you.

7.3.             Upon request, your data may be made available in a pay-per-view format, readable for you and for a subsequent service Provider, to allow for rapid transmission.

7.4.             In the event of violations of data protection regulations, you are entitled to exercise your right of appeal, which you can exercise with the responsible supervisory authority, the Hamburg Commissioner for Data Protection and Freedom of Information https://www.datenschutz-hamburg.de.

  8. **                 Cookies**

8.1.             The portal uses so-called “cookies” in several places. They serve, amongst other things, to make the portal’s offer more user-friendly, effective and secure. Cookies are textual information that a website transmits to the cookie file of the browser on your computer’s hard drive or other device, so that the website may, amongst other things, remember which device has accessed it. A cookie typically includes the name of the domain from which the cookie originated, the “lifetime” of the cookie, and a value, usually a randomly generated, unique number. The portal uses the following types of cookies:

8.1.1.         **Session Cookies:** These are temporarily stored cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser until you leave the website. Session cookies make it possible to identify the device during the period of use. This information will not be saved after you leave the site.

8.1.2.         **Persistent Cookies:** These remain for a long time in the cookie file of your browser. The time frame involved depends on the “lifetime” of the particular cookie. After the expiration of this lifetime, the cookie deletes itself. The purpose of using these permanent cookies is to ensure the functionality of the portal (e.g. affiliate tracking in order to sustain useful coupons and offers for our users). The persistent cookies contain no personal data. Name, IP address etc. are not stored in it.

Cookies used are described in further detail in the Cookie Policy of the site at <https://savings-united.com/cookies-policy/>

8.1.3.         **Web Beacons:** These are electronic characters (also called “Clear GIFs” or “Web Bugs”) that allow us to count the number of users who have visited the portal.

8.2.             If you do not wish to accept cookies or web beacons, you may decline them and deny access to previously stored information by setting your web browser accordingly. The settings within your web browser that allow you to do so vary from browser to browser, they can usually be found under “Privacy” or “Cookies” of the “Internet Options” or “Properties” menu of your browser. If you need help turning off cookies, you should use the “Help” menu within your browser. Please note, however, that if cookies and / or web beacons are turned off, you may not be able to use all features of the portal.

8.3.              **Google Analytics**

The Provider uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google Inc., 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). Google Analytics also uses cookies (see the description in section 8.1.), which allow an analysis of the use of the portal by you. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the portal is usually transmitted to a Google server in the USA and stored there. IP anonymization has been activated on this portal so that the IP address of the users of Google within Member States of the European Union or in other contracting states of the Agreement on the European Economic Area is shortened beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP address be sent to a Google server in the US and shortened there. On behalf of the Provider, Google will use this information to evaluate your use of the portal, to compile reports on website activity and to provide other services related to website activity and internet usage to the Provider. The IP address provided by Google Analytics as part of Google Analytics will not be merged with other Google data.

You can prevent the storage of cookies through a setting of your browser software; However, the Provider informs you that in this case, you may not be able to use all the functions of this website to the fullest extent. In addition, you can prevent the collection by Google of the data generated by the cookie and related to your use of the portal (including your IP address) as well as the processing of this data by Google by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available under the following link:

[_https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en_](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) _._

8.4.                 **Embedded Youtube Videos**

Youtube videos are embedded on this page. It uses the advanced privacy mode, so that when you visit the page with the embedded Youtube video, no cookies are set by Youtube. Submission of data to Youtube and DoubleClick (Alphabet / Google Group companies) will only take place when the video is started

8.4.                 **Use of Google Maps**

Embedded on this website is a map of Google Maps, a service of Google LLC, 1600 Amphitheater Parkway, Mountain View, CA 94043, USA (“Google”). No user data will be transmitted to Google if you only look at the map. Once you click on the map, data can be transferred to Google Maps.

  9. **            Affiliate marketing**

Affiliate Networks offer Affiliate marketing. It is a web-based form of distribution, which allows commercial operators of websites, the so-called merchants or advertisers, to show advertising, which will be paid mostly through click or sale commissions, on third-party Internet sites that are also called affiliates or publishers. The Merchant provides through the affiliate network an advertising medium, such as an advertising banner, voucher or other suitable means of Internet advertising, which is subsequently integrated by an affiliate on its own Internet pages or via other channels such as keyword advertising or e-mail marketing.

  10. **              Modification of this Privacy Policy**

The Provider reserves the right to adjust security and privacy measures, as required by technical or legal developments. In these cases, the Provider will also adapt this privacy statement accordingly. Please note the current version of our privacy policy.

  11. **              Questions and contact**

You have a right to free information about the data stored with the Provider to your person as well as a right to correct, block or delete this data. For questions about the collection, processing or use of your personal data, information, correction, blocking or deletion of data and revocation of any given consent or objection to a particular use of data, please contact **contact@savings-united.com**.

  12. **             Data protection in applications and in the application process**

The provider collects and processes the personal data of applicants for the purpose of processing the application process. The processing can also be done electronically. This is particularly the case if an applicant submits corresponding application documents to the controller by electronic means, for example by e-mail or via a web form available on the website. If the controller concludes a contract of employment with an applicant, the data transmitted will be stored for the purposes of the employment relationship in accordance with the law. If no employment contract is concluded with the candidate by the controller, the application documents will be automatically deleted two months after the announcement of the rejection decision, unless deletion precludes other legitimate interests of the controller. Other legitimate interest in this sense, for example, a burden of proof in a procedure under the General Equal Treatment Act (AGG).
